

- 3013127037
- jhwperea@gmail.com
- Portafolio Github
- /jhonierperea

EDUCATION

Algorithmics: Python y Javascript (2023)

Francisco José de Caldas University.

Technology in Analysis and Development of Information Systems. (2013)

National Learning Service (SENA)

SKILLS

Responsive Web Design

Digital Marketing

Search Engine Optimization

Frontend: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Vue, Nuxt, Bootstrap, Material Design Frameworks.

Backend: Php, MySQL, PostgreSQL, NodeJS CRM's knowledge

Inglés B2

JHONIER ALEJANDRO PEREA DERAZO

Software Developer

ABOUT ME

I have worked in software development since 2013, for some companies and also as a freelancer, acquiring both backend and frontend skills and notions of graphic design, enthusiastic about user experience and agile data management.

JOB EXPERIENCE

O BLUEDATA (COSMITET) Dec 2023 - Current

Web Development: Wordpress, Php, NodeJs, Sass, VueJs, Angular, Responsive Web Design, Pixel Perfect.

blueweb - STP NETWORKS

Jul 2022 - Jul 2023

Custom Templates based on Wordpress CMS:

- STP Networks: Wordpress, Php, NodeJs, Sass, VueJs, Angular, Responsive Web Design, Pixel Perfect.
- Blueweb: C#, Umbraco CMS, Stripe, Bootstrap, Material Design.

SOLUPROPERTY

Sept 2018 - May 2022

Application development for attendance management, forums, assemblies and meetings: NodeJS, VueJs, Laravel, Php.

♦ Q&P GROUP

Sept 2019 - Apr 2020

Application development for hotel management, reservations, staff, kitchen: Laravel, VueJs, NodeJs and Amazon Web Services.

/Previous Jobs